welcome to another edition of the
boutique articles today's episode is
episode 2 and I'm taking you through a
day in my life
I think they pointed me to be this is
gonna suffice for an intro for now
[Music]
needless to say I keep her check she was
a bad bad nevertheless calling it quits
now baby all right crash at my place
baby all right
you know jack she was
[Music]
reckon tres aka the glue guy and today
you're gonna see a day in the life of
yours truly now admitting Lee my days
are pretty consistent I love what I do
I love working I my life is not the most
exciting I don't do a ton of fun stuff
but it's fun to me because I'm so
passionate about strength and
conditioning so you'll see you'll see me
in the morning conducting some business
related stuff be on the phone I'll take
you to the glue lab you'll see me
working with clients you'll see me train
the glute squad and you'll also watch me
lift weights with my training partners
and finally we will end the night with
what I also love to do with examining
some research so today's Instagram post
that I have ready is on good coaching
versus bad coaching and I'm really
hoping that this this makes a big
difference and wakes up some of these
competitors and makes them realize why
my coach is actually doing me more harm
than good and I never realized how bad
the coaching was out there so I started
working with hundreds of competitors
once I moved out here to San Diego I
started working with so many bikini
competitors and figure competitors and I
started witnessing what the coaches do
and it's really really bad and there's a
better way so I'm hoping that this post
makes a positive difference hey damn
good to see you
Oh cryotherapy my pleasure I love
hearing this stuff it's a word with a
lot of hip replacement surgery people
and you know it's still amazes me that
this stuff isn't common knowledge to
start out with feet elevated glute
bridges that's easier that's like doing
a tour so elevated push up you know so
elevate the feet start up with that
bilateral so that was coach Dan John and
if you don't know who he is he's one of
the most respected straight coaches in
the world and we keep in touch he was
calling me to thank me for my help with
his hip replacement surgery he had one
hip replaced you know like a decade ago
and it was hell and then this new hip
that he's getting replace it's gonna be
a breeze because he's been training his
glutes properly and as doctors very
impressed but if he would have told me
you know 15 years ago that one day Dan
John would be facetiming me I would be
blown away you know it's such an honor
to work with these people now that were
my idols and now they see me as an equal
and it's it's so meaningful and such an
honor for me I can't even I can't you
know I never take that for granted
oh good old Omar
so my friend Omar just made a point
poking fun of all the people who just
repackage my stuff Brian played off as
their own which never used to bother me
in my entire career but lately on
Instagram it is frustrating when you see
people that just blatantly copy my own
programs and stuff verbatim and then
they don't even credit me but this seems
to be the new age with Instagram and we
feel like on Facebook we used to have a
policing system but now Facebook has
changed and I don't even go on Facebook
anymore so the police is gone and this
is kind of the way things are for the
time being so but yeah this is a funny
pose
your sunflower
I think you'll ever be too much or you
be left in that unless I stop by
give the sample
[Music]
we got here
it's a part act natural
try says and front doubts before peppers
and then one short with fatiguing the
quad before the disband and elderly but
reverie when I made that post there was
no research at that time I don't think
so imagine it we both hit triceps first
with numbers with nobody with no ones by
these like scaring fear-mongering
articles you know they're out there like
those they're dangerous you look at that
survey and it's like no one without
dangerous at all interested in all right
what's the most dangerous enemies that
is the most dangerous for the low
priority
the statements are wrong that when we
they recorded their number of injuries
before you get a sense ooh can we get
Wi-Fi man young my trainers favorite day
[Music]
[Laughter]
but the good news is I got you a job
right in front of the speech go grab a
sappy foot that's because it's easier
than unlike his best features yeah buddy
in the name of a plant
what's up guys today I'm going to talk
about blog posts that I just posted so
this video will be embedded in it and
this is on an eight-week experiment that
I just ran hopefully you can see them
stepping up I just got this mic
four years I got roasted on YouTube for
not having a microphone so hopefully
this helps we should begin with the hip
thrusts and move on to a new circle flop
okay so it's us tonight this what we
need to do some different stuff as far
as
later Anthony did I tell you guys a one
Thursday when you guys went there I just
give an hour straight ahead for us
variations like five or six at the
[Music]
my main goal is to get you guys strong
and hip doesn't your like I don't want
you using Smith machine here and then
okay your gym doing something different
than always doing different stuff like
one thing I noticed when I was first
start working with Briana I'm asked that
back in the day when they won't train
with me but I train them like three
weeks in a row and then I get them up to
like using like four or five for hit us
and then they would then I would see
them for a couple weeks and then they'd
be back to using like 365 and [__]
without me then you won't push yourself
as hard at hip dress it's a most
important exercise for your glutes and I
like Nordics for your hammy so you gotta
push those all the time and you go to
figure out convenient ways to do them at
your gym that's one thing that not
everyone is good at I'll talk to them
like well my gym it doesn't really have
a good place I'm like you know things
are too narrow
[Music]
the first thing we always do is why we
do have the any Impreza necessary
[Music]
the 405 arrests their throat
3-nothing right one two three go it's
been a long day it's about 8:30 p.m. and
I am exhausted so therefore I'm going to
7-eleven my home away from home and I'm
going to pick up an energy drink
you always got to get to
- 4:29
all right don't you love each other
[Music]
clapping a demon on God looking like a
fraud
[Music]
so should I want to show so I'm back
home and now it's time to hit the books
everyone in Fitness loves lifting
weights that's easy but what separates
the wheat from the chaff so you see I've
never heard a lot wheat Yesi separates
the wheat from the chaff chaff Shafer
chaff lose the chaff of wheat shell sort
the valuable from the worthless yep I
just need to know how to pronounce chief
chaff lease hf and for you youngsters
you don't know what that means it means
the separate the valuable from the non
valuable is your scientific knowledge
you got to hit the books you should
spend an equal amount of time studying
as you do lifting this is in med size
sports exercise and the title is
evidence for an upper threshold for
resistance training volume in train
women in this study lasted six months
that's unheard of you never see six
month long studies but for six months
they had four groups one group performed
five total sets another group did ten
another group fifteen another twenty now
all sets were carried out to failure the
study showed that the best results were
seen with a ten set group anyway this is
just one study that I'll be going over
tonight I'll be going over a few and I
am equally as committed to staying on
top of the research as I am staying in
shape it's been a long day
this guy's calling it a night I hope you
enjoyed the video please comment below
and let me know what other things you'd
like to see
thank you for watching
[Music]